

AVRAM STERN Full Stack Developer

O San José Costa Rica

% (506) 8816-5476

SOCIAL

@stern9

in @stern9

https://stern9.dev/

PROFILE

More than 7 years of experience, working with different brands such as American Express, Delta, Kellog's, Dunkin Donuts, Playstation and others. Using agile methodologies on a daily basis for different projects. Fast learner looking forward to keep on acquiring new knowledge throughout my career.

EDUCATION

High-School Degree
British School of Costa Rica

1994 - 2007

1994 - 2007

Bachelor Degree - Business

Management

Universidad Interamericana 2011

Bachelor Degree - Computer
 Science

Ulacit

2016

SKILLS

- JavaScript🖪 React&
- NodeJS®
- HTML 目
- Express
- CSS 5
- Unix**⊡**
- Git 🏵

EXPERIENCE

Manager

From 2009 to 2012 | Don Doner Restaurant

Provisioning SEO

From 2012 to 2013 | Local Splash

Delivering the best results for the company and improving productivity.

Media Operations Technology Analyst

From 2013 to 2015 | Bosz Digital/Prodigious

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

Associate Creative Engineer

From 2015 to 2016 | Prodigious

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

Creative Engineer

From 2016 to 2018 | Prodigious

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

Senior Creative Engineer

From 2018 to 2021 | Prodigious

Work in this company dedicating the best responsibility in the area that corresponds.

CERTIFICATES

- International Baccalaureate Diploma
- IGCSE Certificate

REFERENCES

Marketing Ops Manager

Tennessee Grimes

Phone: (773) 319-7070

Email: tennessee.grimes@gmail.com

QA Manager

Wendy Hidalgo

Phone: (506) 8701-5926

Email

wendy.hidalgo@groupeconnect.com

LANGUAGES

- EnglishSpanish
- French

INTERESTS

Music

₹ Travel

Read

Sports